Well, my car is currently at the service center
[music]
I am leaving the train at the service center for that movie, so
when will you get it, a week, you will
stay aside, it is being taken out, there is Diwali also, you will get
time because of that, sir, come on come
brother, brother, it is good, it will be
closed here right now, it is Kali Puja, that is why I will get it
after Kali Puja, you are depositing the car right now
because yesterday I got a call and they
said that people said that you mean will you
deposit it now or after Diwali,
so I said that brother, I was
very worried about the car for the last 3 months, I was not
getting any party, right now I don't want any problem, deposit the car
first, so I have
deposited the car by putting it on insurance claim, it will remain
closed for now, it means it will open for you,
which is usually after two weeks, then I will get the car, so that's it, bye
-bye ATM